"Yamada Cram School"
"Accepting new students"
Uh, um... This is my first day here, and...
You must be Mr. Kagaya. Nice to meet you.
Your parents told me you'd be coming.
Hmm?
Oh, there was a supermarket
I'd never seen before on the way here.
They don't have these flavors
at the one by my house, so...
Plus both my parents work, you know.
I can teach you some
simple recipes for next time.
If you're interested, of course.
Huh?
We've even got a kitchen in the back!
In a cram school?
Yep, in a cram school. Pretty weird, huh?
Sounds like everyone's here.
Let me introduce you!
Shuichi... Shuichi!
Shuichi! Are you okay?! It's me!
Do you recognize me?
A dream?
Huh?
I feel like I had a weird dream...
Did I just imagine it?
I can't remember it at all...
Oh! Where's Yoshioka?!
Oh, hey.
Uh, please look away.
Oh, but you don't have your glasses on.
I guess it's okay.
Glasses?
Oh, you mentioned it earlier--
when we were looking for my wallet.
Oh, did I?
You're awake, huh?
Found your clothes! Here.
And I found your wallet, too.
It was in the rubble over there.
What're you...?
We can talk it over once we're back
with everyone else, okay?
You're one of us now, too.
Okay, Shuichi, let me ask you again.
You don't remember any of
what happened before you passed out?
That's right.
Yoshioka, same for you?
Huh? Umm, yeah.
Once we entered the forest,
there was a boy holding Yoshioka's
wallet--we think he was Clair's ally.
He suddenly turned into a monster, grabbed us...
And then, I feel like he just... crushed us.
That's all I remember.
And yet, here you are, standing in front of us.
Was there only one of them?
She wasn't there, was she?
Yes... I think.
It's your fault!
You knew they were dangerous!
But you ran in on your own
and put Yoshioka in danger!
Stop it, Ikeuchi!
He's right. Shuichi's actions
were extremely dangerous.
Still... I kinda like him.
At least, more than someone
who'd just abandon his friends.
I didn't do that!
They're safe. We got the wallet back.
All's well that ends well. Right?
I'm Yota Murakami. Nice to meet you.
Shuichi Kagaya.
I think you'll be a worthy rival.
What?
Um...
N-Nice to meet you, Shuichi!
My name's Isao Kasuga.
Huh?
Oh, was that a weird way to introduce myself?
No, I just thought you'd be... bigger.
Yeah... My monster form looks tough,
but I'm not much of a fighter.
I actually like flowers and plants.
He's got crazy powers, though!
He can grow plants and alter earth at will!
That's right!
These are for you.
Oh... Thanks.
Sorry if I'm wrong here, but...
Did you go to Yamada Cram School
when you were little?
Yeah. How did you know?
I live around there...
I used to see you hanging out
with all your friends.
I never talked to you guys or anything,
but you all seemed to have
a lot of fun--I kind of envied you.
That's weird. I never hung out
with anyone at cram school.
Oh?
I was the only student at Yamada Cram School.
Maybe you're remembering
some other group of friends.
Oh, really? That's weird. But, yeah. Mmm-hmm.
I mean, if you say so.
I must be thinking of something else.
Why don't you say hello, Aihara?
I'm fine, thanks.
That sounded like a girl... But...
Don't be shy, now!
Oh!
Come on out, Aihara!
Ugh...
Presenting Miku Aihara!
She can turn invisible! Jealous?
I wish I'd thought of that power.
You could do all kinds of naughty stuff!
Definitely one of the most
useful powers out there!
Oh... Yeah.
I feel like I've seen her somewhere before.
Welcome.
--Huh?
Would you like me to heat this up?
--Oh! You're from the convenience store!
Is that enough?
She disappeared!
I suppose I should introduce myself too.
I'm Sayaka Koyanagi, the leader of the team.
She's a total lesbo.
Oh!
Let's get back on topic.
Here's what probably happened:
The two of you were grabbed by
that boy and passed out.
But then, some other force appeared,
and they started fighting.
In the ensuing chaos, you were
forgotten and spared because of it.
That makes sense.
One thing's for certain:
There was a huge fight there.
Maybe a war between two big teams, or something.
You mentioned your sister before, right?
She probably came back with her friends.
Y-Yeah! That must be it!
Yeah, that seems likely.
It appears the fight over the coins
is more heated than we thought.
However, we must not run from it.
We can't let dangerous people
like them gain that power!
After all, it's the coins we're after.
Strength will not always be the deciding factor.
We have our own way of fighting.
Can I ask a question?
What is it?
You've shown us your powers,
so now--just to prove we're on your side--
we'll show you ours.
Ready, Shuichi?
Oh, okay.
That's an impressive skill.
Does that give you an idea?
Yes... With you on our side,
our strength improves greatly.
Well, Yota? Do you think you could take them?
Hmm, I don't know. I'm not too confident.
Want to give it a try?
I'll pass. I don't want to get hurt.
Those marks...
Well, I'm sure you two will be a big help.
The sun is going down. Let's call it a day.
Wait a second.
You know, don't you?
You remember what happened out there.
I'm the same as Shuichi.
I don't remember anything.
Liar.
Are you upset that I went inside of Shuichi?
Please, you aren't enough.
Shuichi needs me. Nobody can replace me.
Without me, he's not capable
of fighting or hurting others...
Just as I thought:
You two are completely different.
You two cannot become one.
She must be mad...
Mad at me for running off
into danger like that without her.
Shuichi...
Are you hungry?
This is nice.
There's something appealing
about eating in a place like this.
Well? You have something
you want to say to me, don't you?
Who was better? Me... Or that girl?
She went inside you, didn't she?
And she was naked.
No! I mean she kind of had to...
Had to? So, is that why you let me in, too?
Well...
Hey.
If you want to, I can do something
that'll make you feel even better...
Hah! Just kidding.
The noodles are getting soggy. Let's eat.
I can tell. That girl is lying.
Yota said that was a fight between two teams.
But if it was, there should have
been more blood and footprints around.
She showed up and fought to save them?
But... Hmm...
You two cannot become one.
Hey, is that you, Abukawa?
What are you doing out here?
Kaga! What are you doing?
Taking a walk. It's hot,
and I couldn't sleep, so...
I think it got hit by a car.
I was on a walk to and found the thing.
I couldn't just leave it, you know?
Let me help.
--Huh?
--Here.
Don't worry about it. I've only got one.
But...
What's wrong, Kaga?
Nothing...
Man, you really do look like
a different person without your glasses!
Oh, yeah?
For real? You'll get arrested!
Nah, for real!
Oh, what up, Abukawa?
Do you know them?
Yeah, I guess.
Thanks for your help!
What is that? Why are you up
at the buttcrack of dawn?
Glad to see you, man!
Go buy me a drink or something!
Psh. You trying to bum
money off a high schooler?
"The following day -- After school"
That dead animal... Did he...?
No, that's ridiculous.
But Abukawa was like a
totally different person last night...
Ugh!
What is wrong with this thing?
Okay, it's fixed!
Thank you!
So, uh, Mifune...
Hmm? What is it?
Nevermind.
If something's bothering you, you can tell me!
Thanks.
Oh my god! Now he's with another girl!
He might look tame, but he's a real shithead!
That was close!
Okay, once Yoshioka and the others see this--
What's wrong? Say something!
Can't talk without the
freckled freak by your side?
You weren't the one that killed Sudo, huh?
His body was cut clean
in half by some kind of blade.
That's not the way you were fighting yesterday.
Spit it out! What are you plotting?!
Did you tell them about Sanbe?
No.
You're right, it wasn't me.
We happened on his body in the forest,
and Clair grabbed the phone off of him.
You're not lying, are you?
Either way, you entered Koyanagi's pact.
You can't betray us now.
What does she mean, "big help"?!
Don't you get cocky!
You can't even fight unless someone helps you!
That's right.
That's why I can do things
that can't be done alone.
That must be what it means.
My power is not for me.
It exists to protect "normal"
people--the powerless ones.
It must be for someone...
Someone in this story...
Your phone keeps buzzing, it's annoying.
Who is this?
Ah, hello.
My name is Chihiro Yoshioka.
I'm an acquaintance of Shuichi's...
Uh, hello?
I'm sorry, I don't like talking
to people I don't know.
I'll call you back later.
Huh? Wai--
Was that Naoto calling you?
No. I'm going to leave for a bit.
You need to go to bed.
Don't treat me like a kid.
Hello! I, uh--
Are you the girl who was one with Shuichi?
So... You do know what that was.
Shuichi and I were completely together as one.
Our spirits, bodies...
Even our memories blended into one.
We were neither me nor him.
What happened to us? Please tell me!
That is a special power...
A power that only Shuichi has.
He joins with someone,
and their strength is combined...
This allows them to exceed
their limits and achieve their goal.
It's an extremely powerful ability...
As long as the two have the same goal.
Tell me, how did you get this number?
I never gave it to my sister.
I got it from Shuichi.
I don't believe it.
There's no way Shuichi
could remember this number.
Say something silly like
that again, and I'll kill you.
When I became one with him,
I saw his memories and noticed it then.
There are shadows in his memories--
shadows of things erased unnaturally.
"I hung out with **** today."
There are shadows in his memories--
shadows of things erased unnaturally.
"I hung out with **** today."
I don't think even he would notice.
"I ****ed ****'s clothes" "**** was smiling"
"**** was having fun ****" "**** said **** liked it"
"Me and ****'s present"
I don't think even he would notice.
"**** is always so nice" "On the way home **** and I ****"
"talked about when we were at"
"all **** or like ****ed" "Me and **** went to ****"
I don't think even he would notice.
"went to hang out at ****"  "when I tried to ****"
"I did that with **** but"  "was worried about me and"
I don't think even he would notice.
"kind of embarrassed but I ****"
"****'s hand"
Only someone viewing his memories
objectively, from outside, could tell.
"a **** was ****"
"It **** with"  "**** also ****"
Only someone viewing his memories
objectively, from outside, could tell.
"****ed *****"
"was ****'s"  "did **** ****"
Only someone viewing his memories
objectively, from outside, could tell.
Those shadows... I don't know
how or why they were erased.
However...
You and the shadows look the same.
His memories might disappear,
but maybe there are some spaces
in Shuichi's heart that can't be blacked out.
"I miss ****"
It wasn't all of them, they were fragmented--
But as I filled those shadows with you,
I was able to see Shuichi's lost memories.
I haven't told Shuichi
about this or anyone else.
He doesn't remember anything
from the time when we were one.
But I know! You're not a bad person!
I mean, for Shuichi,
nobody could take your place!
Please, join us! If we work together,
we can stop this conflict!
The power the alien talked about...
What if someone actually got power that--
How many gatherers have you encountered so far?
Huh?
The alien said you need 100 coins, right?
Do you think gathering that
many coins is actually impossible?
What are you...?
What if someone had already gathered 100 coins?
And what if the world was already on
the brink of destruction because of them?
I'm sorry. I cannot join you.
Shuichi and I have different goals now.
Who were you talking to?
It doesn't concern you.
Is that so?
I heard we lost a kill today.
Subaru says they were pretty tough,
but suddenly collapsed--
And as he was about to finish them,
you stepped in and stopped him.
Does that not concern us, either?
Elena...
I know.
I haven't forgotten my role.
We are here to gather coins.
If someone gets in our way, we eliminate them--
No matter who it is.
Only five.
That's how many coins we've found
since we came here two months back.
At this rate, we'll never collect 100.
But we've learned something.
If you put together the locations
of the first coins we collected,
and the ones we found in the forest,
a pattern emerges.
The trail of the fallen spaceship.
That's right. The thing we're
after is the ship itself.
If we can get there,
we can gather 100 coins.
"Episode 9: Staked Claims"